Brian Connors

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



Work History

BULLS EYE PEST CONTROL

2014-2018

Pest Control Technician 2014-2018
With this job I mainly worked alone as I spent the entire day driving from home to home treating our customers homes with their various pest problems. This taught me the value of time management as I had a set list of services to complete each day without any management supervision.

HOMEFRONT PEST CONTROL

2012-20014

pest control technician

Same overall job description and experience as Bulls Eye

ALBERTSONS

2007-2012

courtesy clerk/ cashier/ service deli tech/ night crew stocker/ produce clerk/ dairy clerk Over the course of my employment here I worked in various departments. Most of them involved stocking shelves efficiently while still greeting customers and providing excellent customer service in a timely, friendly manner.

Notable Skills

-JavaScript/ES6 -MongoDB -React -mySQL

-React Redux -CSS/LESS/SASS/HTML

-React Router -bootstrap

-Express -GIT
-Node.js -Jira
-loopback -JQuery

Personal Profile

I have worked in the retail and pest control industry for a combined 11 years now. With those careers I have developed customer service and time management skills to complete projects on time. However, neither of these careers were satisfactory to me. With that being said, I look forward to a career in computer programming.

Contact Details

Brian Connors 31011 Jedediah Smith Rd Temecula, CA. 92592 seahorse8789@gmail.com 951 240 0056

Education

Temecula Valley High School 2004-2008 Diploma

Origin Coding Academy certificate of completion

2018